Okay, all right. We are going to call to order today's regular meeting of the Miami City Council for Tuesday, April 3.
Second item on the agenda in the NELAMM 2016 wrestling team proclamation.
And that's the city council and I think what we do with the proclamation.
Okay, all right.
And coach, do you want to come up and introduce your guys and tell us a little bit about the success you had this year?
We've all heard about it though. We still want to give you a chance to brag about it.
I didn't have anything prepared, I feel so bad right now.
I will definitely make deals. That's I can.
Definitely want to thank everybody for the opportunity and the recognition of these young men and what they've done.
Like I told our team today before we got here is I wish we could bring all of you.
And what sometimes our guys don't understand is and everybody understand is it's not necessarily the eight all Americans that we have present here.
But it's the entire team and the entire opportunity that we were granted from everyone.
But thank you guys so much for the chance.
I hope they realize it as much as I do that it's not something that comes every day.
But we'll kind of start over here and correct me.
We'll start with our lightest guy.
He's our 125 pounder.
He finished seventh this year at the National Tournament force.
After that we've started up at 33.
And now they're not the same size that they were whenever they were.
So you're looking at him and saying 133 pounder now he's more like about 155.
He's the right guy.
Oh, he's gay.
He's lying to me.
No, they do.
He finished for that.
He finished fourth for this year.
141 pounder mid-stellar.
He finished fifth for this year.
Actually he ended up getting the most falls award of the whole National Tournament.
Most falls, least amount of time.
Which if you know anything about Russell and scores you a lot of big time points.
Very fortunate to have him on our team.
149 pounder is Christian Holden.
He actually, and I don't know if he realizes this or not yet either.
But he vests over the National Tournament with a broken arm.
He dislocated his elbow about January 10th.
And whenever you dislocated it's so bad that he broke the tip of his radius off.
And that wasn't officially healed before he went to the Regional Tournament.
I don't think he cares.
But Russell and National Tournament had he not had that broken arm.
I think he had been a national champion like some of these other young men that we have.
But he still scored some big time points for us.
Very fortunate to have him on part of our organization.
157 pounder is actually...
coming back from a trip from North Carolina, kind of a good thing.
They didn't win the national title last night against Villanova.
He might've been caught up in the hoop floor and everything else.
Probably a song, a party that he was a part of, but he actually, as soon as he got back
from the airport, made his second trip to OU, entertaining the idea of either OU or North
Carolina at the moment, but he's not with us.
He's a returning, or he's a national champ for us.
174 pounder Jacobi Smith, this young man, is actually a two-time national champ, wow, incredible.
He was the OUW, the whole Russell and Tournament, lights out, Russell very, very well
for us for a very fortunate to have him and very fortunate to have him be a part of our team.
184 pounder Jacobi Hill, he finished four process year, Jacob has been actually with us for the
last three years, been here since we reinstated the program at NEL, he registered his
first year, second year, Russell for us, and then this year he's a fourth place as an
all-American at the National Tournament, 197 pound, he's Josh Lachum, he's from Chickashe
Oklahoma, finished eight fourths this year, kind of had an injury there that kept him from
doing as well as I thought he could have done, which I know he could have done, and he doesn't
like it's 197 pound either, he's like a lot bigger than me, and last but not least certainly
Blake Andrews, he's our heavyweight, he does like a heavyweight, I was sitting there behind him and
seeing that being his back, he's a big young man, he's a national champ for us also, looking at both
of these young men are looking at going to Oklahoma State next year, we've got a lot of the
guys that some of our sophomores that are moving on, he's going to be back next year,
better be back next year, he'll be back next year, Jacob is looking at a couple other different
places, several different places that has opportunities with Christian the same thing,
mid to same way, and then Josh the same way, but back to my whole point of what I was talking
about with our team, and we instilled this team by, we instilled this family tradition value amongst
our guys, and it's just sad that this isn't big enough for all of them to be in here, or we
would have everyone of them because if you notice any of the pitchers on Facebook or the Twitter,
everyone of these guys are just as much responsible for this national championship that we
won as the 8-O Americans that we have here, the 9-O Americans total, the 10 national qualifiers,
and I couldn't be more proud, I'm looking around, and I'm seeing guys that were out there
and the hearts for hammers, they do a lot of community service, they do a lot of things in the
community, and I know they would do it without the guidance of us, but a lot of that
comes from the guidance of the coaching staff, which I didn't introduce coach Dennis Sigmund,
this year I wanted to ward up the most outstanding, what is the most outstanding coach.
That's actually not my word that is Coach Sigmund's a word.
We also have three other assessment assistants that are very, very diligent in what they do with
our coach and staff two younger, two younger guys, one of them that's younger, but actually
my age, I say, is younger, but all four of our assistant coaches actually bring home the
gold medals that I claim, you know, honors for, but we're very fortunate to have the situation
very fortunate that we brought back wrestling to NEO and as long as I'm here, we're going
to make sure that we keep a winning tradition involved with the program.
Thank you guys.
Thank you, Coach.
Thank you.
Congratulations to all of the young men.
Okay, I didn't really recognize for all council member Joe Sharber for his, he was a sort
of a show.
Can you come up please?
Yeah.
I'm going to do this.
Joe is one of those guys and it was kind of a good fruit.
Come up here, Joe.
We had an opening on the council and it was one of those last minute things and actually a member of
staff said, we're going to be able to talk about doing this, so he gave me a call and I ended up
up with doing this sort of, and it's sort of another term, that some health issues had to
take a break for a while.
But he made me back someday, and we're not sure if that's between him and his wife and son.
But I wanted to prepare this for him and I wrote on here, Joe, thank you very much for your service.
You always put the taxpayers first and that's what many good great council member.
And that is so true.
For all of these taxpayers watching, I'm going to need to put it out there.
Joe can squeeze the bottom of the door.
And always, every budget cycle, he asked questions and he wanted to understand, and I was
a talk that this would be wanted to do about, it's so hard to come in as a brand new councilman
and come in the first meeting and by and in six weeks later, he asked a woman that, let's talk to
you.
It's tough to understand.
I can't take you at least in here to understand what's going on.
It's going on.
The Joe was a tremendous councilman.
And this is well-deserved.
So I'm going to take the staff to make sure everything is working out.
Thank you very much.
Okay, another recognition, Kim Shepherd for 10 years of service and I believe Mike Edwards is going to be the owner of
Good, I skip Robert I do I don't know back to Robert is kidding there
And so James yes
Do the honors this is kids Shepherd. I think everybody knows him as cowboy every in the whole city
I don't know. It's a tough choice between Joe and cowboy here who knows how many most people in the city
So the Cowboys been with us for 10 years. He actually started at the Civic Center
And then he went to parks that he's went to the cemetery now
He has actually came back to parks
He has five kids
Been married two years now and he's got four grandkids
So let's pleasure to have him on our team and you were a lot of learning a little of your
Miami club. Yes, he was he was the president first president in the city here
Well congratulations, can't thank you
Now you said you were never short for words
Okay, and I don't need to skip over a while about it a Robert and
Mike you guys will come up
You're leaving mayor council. We're here tonight. Robert barbers ten years with us
Robert is a lead man on our crew and he's our heavy equipment operator. He does a great job
If we have a
anywhere in the city if we have a issue we need to dig around a lot of
Utilities and stuff like that we call on our Albert. He's the guy we go to he's one of them like it happened not tear stuff
Robert has two children and three grand sons
Two of his grand sons were born this month and one of them was born on his birthday
So he's prespecial about that Robert's actually getting married April 30th to his best friend and she's back here as well
He's a very big senior fan and Oklahoma City center fan and in his spare time
He likes to spend the time with his family and grandchildren and kids
One of the things I want to say about Robert is
We try to send the street department guys to OSU to the called L-Tab classes. It's free of charge
All we have to do is pay for him to get out there
It's a 12-step process. We try to send one or two to a couple classes every year
Robert is the only one in auto accounting that has
Completed that program
A lot of the other guys in street department are about halfway through but he's actually completed that only one in auto accounting
Thank you for your service.
Okay, item six is public input on schedule personal appearances only when the audience it wishes to address the council on any of the agenda items
You're being none item. Oh
Hi, huh
Hi, but see you there. Come on up
She's so I would you all can't play in a three-way
So you won't come in a three-minute. I know
So honorable mayor councilman distinguished ladies and gentlemen
well me out and bow well
I am so tickle and happy to see that the new animal shelter is really going to happen
It's not every day that I get to see a dream come true
But I think I'm really going to do it this time
It's happening because you city officials and others really care about the welfare of our neglected abused and homeless animals
While I realize there's never enough money to fix all the problems in the city
You solve the desperate need and you stepped up to the calls
You know the new shelter was something that my late husband can't was passionate about
I know he bugged the heck out of you and everybody else too
From the time he became councilman until his death is mayor he
Had meetings with people and he talked to individuals and then he came home and reported to me
But I didn't mind cuz I was on the same plate, but you know, I sometimes think the like animals better people
What do you think Neil?
Anyway, I'm here tonight just to tell you how grateful I am that you didn't let the shelter fall by the way side
You kept moving forward on it you could have shelter didn't use the money somebody else, but you didn't you stay true to your pledge
And that tells me something about you as men and women
I personally want to extend my gratitude and appreciation to each of you
especially Neil Johnson
Joe Walden, Mike Ferris Tyler, Con just a name of you
So I'm closing
Kent, thanks you but I'll be saying to you the kitty said you and I be a gray mayor. Thanks you
Thank you. Okay, I didn't said it was considered gender. It's not for recommending items 8 through 14 for the consent agenda
There are no questions on the adults. I would entertain emotions to approve most of your print mayor in a second second roll call Johnson
4.5.
Lesson.
So.
Okay.
I'm 15.
I'm excited about this one.
Resolution to recognize the cultural district proposed for the Arts and Humanities Council.
An application to the Oklahoma Arts Council to create and develop a cultural district.
District in downtown Miami.
Thank you for being here.
I'm having Chuck hand out some photographs that we have to include in the grant,
which also includes a match of the proposed cultural district.
So first I would like to say thank you for allowing me to appear before the council and
present this opportunity for a grant to develop a plan for a downtown cultural district.
You have something written in your book.
I believe.
And I thought I would just in my own words go through why this is important and what we're doing.
So through the Miami Arts and Humanities Council,
but in conjunction with the support from the city of Miami,
we are going to apply grant to help us to develop a plan for a cultural district.
So on the plan you can see the district will encompass first street north to second street south as well as from a street to a street.
The reason that a district is designed as such is because it includes the Coleman,
which of course is central to any idea of a cultural district to Miami.
We have worked to public art on the street downtown.
We have Charles Banks Wilson studio, The Dops in Museum,
and the Miami Public Library.
It name a few.
And those are listed on the map, and I think you have a picture of those in the binder as well.
So the grant is a five-year grant, and it is from the Oklahoma Arts Council,
and it begins July of 2016, which is this year.
And at the end of the five years, we will apply for the area to be designated as a cultural district.
So I just want to make that clear.
The grant funds are $7,500 a year, which is going to be matched by funds from the Miami Arts and Humanities Council,
and other sources as well as in kind funds from the city of Miami.
This money that we receive from the Arts Council and that we raise,
will then be used for consulting fees related to planning and branding the district.
The plan will outline activities, events, business development,
all as a result of the cultural opportunities that we already have in Miami.
So you wonder probably why this is important to Miami.
A lot of people might think why does it matter to have a designation of a cultural district in downtown,
because we already have all these wonderful assets.
Well, first of all, it will bring revenue from Miami in the form of increased sales taxes,
and by helping local businesses.
business grow as well as developing new business. The activities and business
will enhance the quality of life for everyone in our town that are an outgrowth of
the planning for the five years. Having a cultural district helps with the recruitment
of new business and people to my Emma. A cultural district is a powerful tool because
more and more people want these activities and resources available in a place where they live
and work. So I'm closing. I would again like to thank you for your consideration of this
grant and the resolution, as well as compliment, Marcia Johnson, our public library
director for her leadership and work on the application. She would have been here tonight,
but I believe she is watching the TV. So my Marcia. And I wanted to open it to questions
that you might have. If any. So and this is a five-year process. And during that five
years we'll be working with a consultant that has experienced developing other cultural
districts. And they'll look at the resources that we have and advise us on how best to put
the district together as that kind of. Correct. And you know, in talking with Marcia and doing some
research and with the State Arts Council they suggested that we would maybe hire a facilitator
and it sounds as if it would be very similar to the city strategic plan that we just finished the process.
And we have a rather large committee, business leaders, arts leaders, other interested party,
city employees and leaders, you know, that will be part of the committee that forms a district.
First start to work on forming the district.
Okay. Any comments?
Just one. I'd like to point out when we were working on the comprehensive plan, we started talking
about a concept called Sense of Place. A lot of people when they talk about a city, they always
talk about quality of life. And frankly quality of life is pretty easy to do. The water is drinkable.
You have a good fire department, a good police department. You know, it's, you know, basic
services are provided. But when you start talking about a sense of place and quality of place,
what you're talking about is something that is unique to that community that makes people remember
that community and want to be part of it. In this area, you see this all over. You see the Northwest
Arkansas and a number of the cities like Bentonville, Rogers,
Joplin with a number of the murals that they're doing in the downtown area and the third Thursday
are walking the takes place, Pittsburgh Kansas with little Balkans days. And it's the type
of thing that people in the community appreciate, enjoy being at, but people outside the community
want to go and be a part of too. It gives a community that identity. And just as Ann said, if you
start having that identity, that also ties into if you have a place to people want to visit,
maybe it's a place people want to live, if it's a place.
people want to live. It's a place people want to invest in and bring their businesses to it.
This was something that our comprehensive plan recognized almost immediately and I just thrilled
that through Anne's efforts and Marcia's efforts that we're bringing this to life. It's worth
doing. Any questions or comments? No sir. Okay. And thank you. Thank you. We have an agenda item for a
resolution. And so do we have a motion to approve the resolution for the cultural arts district?
No, it's to approve. We're going to proceed to call the second motion. Okay. And roll call?
Johnson.
All right. Question.
Four stars. All right.
Show. All right. Thank you.
Item 16 requests for approval to sell fuel at cost for young Eagles event on April 3rd.
2016 is recommended by airport authority board members.
Is that a pattern? Or a child? I haven't. I haven't. I haven't. I haven't. I was not able to be here tonight.
So the event was actually postponed from last weekend because of the weather. And in the past,
this event that's going on by the experimental aircraft association, they get flights to about 50
young children. They volunteer their time. And as part of that, they've asked the city to
sell that at cost for the fuel, which the airport board is recommended and we've done that in the past.
And again, the event has been postponed to this weekend. So it's still up to me for kids to come out and get
free airplane rides and see our airport.
All right. Can you please make sure that that postpone that gets noted? And thank you very much.
From 1 to 5 to. Yes, it is. It's from 1 to 5 at the airport.
Okay. Do we have a motion? Make a motion.
In a second. Second. Role call.
Foraster.
Aye.
Wester.
Johnson.
Aye.
Shul.
Item 17 award.
It's 1661 for all the improvements to the lowest best event in the proof of the contract,
and all for the city of Andrew City Attorney, to sign notice to proceed.
Once all the documents are reviewed, Chuck.
This project received three bids. This is on the alley that's between Main Street and A Street
between Central and First. And again, we got some very good bids on this, the low bidder,
being niece construction, which worked on many of our other projects. So we're very confident in him.
So it's our recommendation to award it to niece construction.
Any questions? No.
We're just a second.
Countly located.
Zina?
Yeah. Zina.
Please.
Is it clear more?
Okay.
I had heard of them.
That's all right. Okay. We had a motion motion in the second. Second.
Roll call. Johnson. Forester.
Right. Western.
All right.
Short. That is for me, sorry.
Yes. Yes.
It's for me. Thank you for clarify.
Most of this matter.
I am 18. You bid 1653 for the animal control shelter.
To lowest investor bidder.
It's Saturday, Chuck and Joe.
Thank you, Mayor. Council.
It's been a long time coming, but we feel pretty confident.
We went out for bids and we came back with full qualified bidders.
A lowest bid being 333,000.
Chuck and I made a few phone calls.
He had listed 70 projects in the last five years.
Some over a million dollars.
Chuck and I called six of those customers, I guess.
And with all positive results.
We called and talked to Jason.
He's the vice president of the American company.
Yes, sir.
The little biter.
And he expressed his understanding to the project.
I felt confident about the project.
The prince documents timelines.
And through our speaking with him,
the full confidence that he can complete the job.
And what is the timeline for an completion?
Do we have one?
I believe it's 120 days from the start of order.
Yes.
Okay.
Any other questions?
Just one more time on the projected area, Joe,
It's going to be south.
Just directly south of the public works building 815D on the crook.
And we do have capability.
If in the future we can build on all.
Yes.
We can build on to the south.
Yeah.
Yes.
And you'll remember leading up to this.
We've done the rezoning for that property as well.
Make sure that it could have gone.
We did it.
What is P.D on that property?
Okay.
Do you want to make the motion?
Well, but first I want to thank Joe and Tyler and Mike Furness and Chuck.
I want to thank Mike Furness and Chuck for getting somebody up.
Forgive me.
But you all been dealing with this for a long time and appreciate.
You have to redo everything on several times and appreciate that.
We all appreciate that.
Thank you.
And with that, I'm making motion.
Okay.
I'll take a roll call.
Johnson.
All right.
Weston.
Foraster.
All right.
Thank you.
I don't know.
Can you do business?
Do you?
No.
You're on it.
Staff of fortune in your pocket.
Any mayor or council?
Can you hear me?
Announcements.
I...
To me.
announcement, there's a voting go on today.
If you have not yet voted, you've got 49 more minutes.
So please find your voting to Washington and vote.
I have a couple.
I want to, I'm very happy for my archatia.
I know this was important to him.
And we appreciate him being on the count.
And being the mayor, we appreciate him.
Second, there's a little girl who got hit last night on the bicycle
and just keep her in your prayers and thoughts,
I wish her the best, no family.
Thank you, Neil.
City manager?
Thank you.
I never think you're on our bell try to move as quickly as possible.
I do want to point out that toward the end of this month on the 26th, 27th, 28th,
has part of our budget agenda.
We are going to be having our budget hearings already that time of the year.
I also want to point out that during that time, they're probably a number of things
that we're going to be including as part of that.
That they're related to the budget and finance here.
One is where you'd like to have a study session during that time with Greg Nito to talk about
bonds.
There's a good opportunity right now.
The market is very low, low percentage for bonds.
You remember we have bond anticipation now itself for Red Roberts and Stadium.
And this would probably be a very good time to go into the market and refinance those into
permanent bonds.
So we have great working on that for you right now.
You might remember we set aside a very large amount of our budget for bolt to have some discussions
about bringing bolt in.
We're at a point right now where we want to talk to you about going out and doing that survey
that we have talked about to see if this is going to be something that's viable for my Emma.
So that's going to be coming up as part of that.
Another thing is we're going to be discussing some items related to City Hall.
So that we've been working quite a bit lately about trying to get a renovation now that
we've decided that this building is structurally sound.
There's some things that are taking place with Glendis retirement that will probably allow some
additional space for the police department and we're really rethinking what we might be able
to do with this building.
Possibly we might be able to do some very meaningful things with this building for a significantly
less amount of money.
So again, those are items that we're going to be discussing.
So please put those on your calendar.
We're not only going to be talking about just the nuts and bolts and probably bring Joe in as
a guest be able to make sure that we're pinching those dimes, but also just some things on the
long term that we've all been looking at and wanting to do for my Emma's part of that.
I also want to point out that we're going to be having a press conference on Friday, but
we've got word that on 2017 we have an NJCA tournament or an auto tournament, but a bowl
game that's going to be coming and speaking of red Roberts and field, a lot of people say
why did you build that just for the high school and just for the college what's great for
both of those.
but it's also for the community.
And one thing that we do want to point out,
and this is not a criticism of the news record at all,
but I think in reading the initial article,
it looks as though this is something that NEO is doing.
It is not, it is something that our CVB,
it's something that the city of Miami doing, is doing.
Now of course, we're going to be cooperating very much with
NEO cooperating very much with my and the schools on this,
but it's going to be something terrific for this community
to have a bowl game in 2017.
It's really something we're very happy with.
And Amanda right now is that a conference on sports marketing.
This is going to tie into a lot of things we talk in the budget
about sports marketing that you already know about.
And she's in Grand Rapids, Michigan.
I asked her what the weather was, and she said last night,
it was $2,000,000.
And since all my relatives are Grand Rapids,
you notice I'm in Oklahoma during this time of the year.
I also just wanted to do a quick thanks to Joe and his staff
for the British dedication yesterday.
That was just such a nice, kind of a topping for that facility.
You go over it every single day, and you don't think much about it.
But again, what a beautiful thing that was from Miami
and also just a good cooperative effort
with one of our Native American tribes, our partners.
And we're seeing more and more of that partnership take place.
Again, Joe was the one that really worked on that.
I'm glad you've gone still here, too, because it was so nice to have you.
And so nice to have you take that plaque off,
because I know that was so important to Canada as well.
But important to all of us, so thank you.
I was done.
I just wanted to point out, and thank Melinda, especially,
because she has been doing such a tremendous job on articles
related to what's going on with FEMA.
And the last two articles that she has written
has given the community a very good understanding
that when I was first interviewed, I talked about,
I think almost one of my first meetings I was at, Mayor,
you were the one that was leading the charge
to have the Tetra Tech Study done.
And now we have FEMA accepting the Tetra Tech Study
and looking at it.
And the important thing with that is, is that if they accept that,
we hope that they will be bringing their maps much further down,
which means that a lot of properties that might have been
did valued, because they were in the flood plane
when they weren't before, can stay out of the flood plane.
And if that works out, this studies
are already paid for itself.
And there are many other things that we want to use the study for,
and a lot of people are accepting the fact
that we had a first-class study done on flood routing,
on the initial river, to look at this problem
from a scientific standpoint.
It's working out very well.
Two or three last things we just wanted to talk about.
No two, excuse me.
I wanted to point out that, starting next week,
you're going to see our crews in the parking lot
by security bank, Osperon, and First Baptist Church.
And the timing on that got pulled up to us a little bit,
but you might remember that this is a cooperative effort with...
security, Osmondruck, and first excuse me, first batch is church, in which they're sharing
costs with us, 50-50 to bring that parking lot back to life.
If you've been on that parking lot, it is indeporable shaded.
I don't think it's been touched, since I was here as a teenager, and it's something that
we understand that we can't go in 100% city funds, but some of the businesses that recognize
that they have, some of the stakers saying they would put up some of the effort to make
this happen.
So the reason it's taking place so quickly is the asphalt company that has been hired
by the three entities that are sharing costs.
They pretty much told us, you need to get it done early in the season, because later in
the season, we're going to be on some big jobs in other places, so we're trying to move
that up.
So if anybody asks you, while we're doing that so quickly, when we do have some street work to be done,
that's basically the reason why, but we'll be getting back to the street work very, very quickly
too.
So just wanted to make you aware, and that's a great thing that we're cooperating with some of our local
partners to make something like that happen.
And then speaking of partners, the Intertribal Council, on the 13th of this month, is going to
be holding a meeting with term-bic authorities in Odawn about improving the intersection at
Steve Owen's 69A in the term-bic, which is desperately needed.
But I wanted to just point out the chief spark when it talked to me and said, basically, they'd
like the city to help bring this about, or at least discuss it.
I know that Chuck has been working on quite a few background information on this, how it can
be done.
We have a couple of developments that are going to be taking place at that corner in the not too
distant future that will be affected by this.
And when you talk about this being the gateway to Miami, and you have to wait two or three cycles
for the light to be able to make a left turn, something needs to be done.
And I want to congratulate Chief Spartman for kind of getting the start of all the tribes
are very much involved in it, but also the trustees placed in us to help bring it about
as well.
So that's something taking place.
And last and absolutely not least, you might recognize the person that said you do my left.
But I do not know that this person is now called the Legal Services Coordinator for the City
of Miami.
She has been a selection for that position.
I think you just accepted the offer today, as a matter of fact.
So as we move ahead with our organizational structures, Kristin, this role is going to become
more and more important, because not only working with the current city attorney on the new
city attorney coming up, but we have other cities or other attorneys that are working for us
in other areas, and she'll provide the kind of coordination that's necessary.
And then looking at Randy, who's wanting to jump ship in August, she's going to be taking
over Randy's role in our contracting and purchasing as well.
So she's going to be eventually moving down to Jill's area and be...
Supervised directly by Jill, but as much of self-stargers you were, I'm not too worried about your
supervision.
We're going to have trouble keeping up with you.
That's enough.
Thank you.
Okay, I don't 23 is executive session for soon on to 25 OS 307 B1 and 307 E and 305.
Do we have a motion to go into executive session for the reasons listed on the agenda?
Okay.
Make motion.
And a second.
Second.
World call please.
Forced in.
Aye.
Johnson.
Be right back.
I don't know.
Okay.
We are out of executive session at 704 PM.
Item 24 is adjourned.
We have motion to adjourned.
Motion to adjourned.
Second.
Aye.
Johnson.
Shows.
Aye.
We are adjourned.
That's all right.
It's on now.
The view is rough off.
Okay.